

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

District 1, Ho Chi Minh City, Viet Nam

□ (+84) 822747499 | ■ thinhngow@gmail.com | ★ thinhcorner.com | • th1nhng0

"We become what we think about"

Summary

3+ years experience specializing in the frontend development, backend. Super nerd who loves Competitive programming. Interested in devising a better problem-solving method for challenging tasks, and learning new technologies and tools if the need arises.

Technical Skills_

Typescript, Javascript, Python, C++, Reactjs, Nextjs, Monorepo, Storybook, Threejs, Tailwindcss, Framer Motion, JAMSTACK, Mysql, Mongodb, Agile, Scrum

Work Experience

King Attorney

Ho Chi Minh City, Viet Nan

FULLTIME FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

Jan. 2021 - now

- Built and deployed a information website about law. Using next js and strapi cms
- Build King Attorney App 5.0 using react native

Embery Australia

REMOTE FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

July. 2022 - Now

- Built many websites about ecommerce, landing page.
- Built a 3D experiment website with Threejs
- · Using docker to setup microservices.
- · Using agile and scrum workflow.

Honors & Awards

NATIONAL

2019 Consolation Prize, National High School Informatics Competition for excellent students.

Viet Nan

DOMESTIC

2022 **1st Prize**, HACKATHON WebDev Adventure2020 **3rd Prize**, Student Informatics Olympiad

UII - VNUHCN

Education

University of Science - VNUHCM B.S. IN MATHEMATICS AND COMPUTER SCIENCE

Ho Chi Minh City, Viet Nam

Oct. 2019 - Now

• GPA 7.5

Extracurricular Activity _____

AI4VN 2022 - VAIPE: Medicine Pill Image Recognition Challenge

Viet Nam

LEADER

Aug. 2022 - Sep. 2022

- Leader of a team of 5 people
- Learning how to build a deep learning model end-to-end and how to manage a small team.